Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative
  - Subseries A: Sheelagh Cabalda, Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS)
    - Student Leaders of Color, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Student Medialian Services, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Student Power Movement Ethnic Groups, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Students of Color & Majors, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Substance Abuse Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Summer Institute on Community Cultural Studies in NYC, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Surveys - OASIS, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Syllabi, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Syllabi, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Syllabi, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - A Teacher's Guide to Surviving and Thriving at A/P/A (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Tony Formerito, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Tseng/May Immigrant Study "Enhancing Educational Experiences at NYU: A Report on Immigration", 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - TSOA Student Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - UConn Storrs Conference, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Under One Roof, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - UVA Conference, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Washington Square News, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Witness Tree - Dr. Rosaking, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - World AIDS Day, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Working Retreat, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - WSN Coverage, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Youth Community Groups, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Tomio Geron, Academic Program Coordinator Asian/Pacific/American Studies Program
    Subseries B contains correspondence, memoranda, and reports related to the further development of the A/P/A studies academic program. This includes new course proposals, staff and faculty job descriptions, the development of a mission statement, departmental magazines, and the creation of an alumni association. These records reflect the planning involved in the ongoing development of the academic program.
    - Alumni Association, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Area/Ethnic Studies, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Artist Programs, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Media Archives, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Related Video Collections, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Asian Council and EQUAL Commission, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Major Development, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Minor Program Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Program Meeting, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Retreat Agenda, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Scripts, circa 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Campomanes, Oscar, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Challenge Fund Grant Application, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Chinese Construction Workers at NYU, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (incoming and outgoing): Dean Santirocco, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Course Descriptions, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Course Proposal, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Curriculum Plan, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Directors Undergraduate Study Meeting Schedule, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - East of California Network, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Events, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Follow Up Items, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Internal Sessions, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - International Visitors Program, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Mission Guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - NYU in Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Office Renovations: General, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Office Renovations: Furniture, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Pan-a-Visions Newsletter: Meeting, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Pan-A-Visions Newsletter: Overview, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Petitions, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Personnel Meeting Agenda, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Post-doctoral Fellow Paper Proposal, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Program Coordinator Position, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Public Events, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Public Programming: Maya Lin, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Reports and Memos: General, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Research, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Research Assistant Job Description, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Staff Meeting Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Student Coordinators, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Student Surveys, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Student Surveys, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Working Session: Colonialism, Diaspora, and the Americas, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Working Session: Community Documentation, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Working Session: Community Studies and Curriculum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Working Session: Curriculum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Working Session: South Asian American Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Subseries C: Risa Morimoto, Administrator and Asian/Pacific/American Institute Coordinator
    Subseries C includes general course information related to the A/P/A program in addition to various events sponsored by the department. This subseries contains syllabi, course evaluations, course proposals and event records.
    - Asian Artists (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Asian Arts Organizations (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Artist-in-Residence: General, Undated, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Artist-in-Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Artists Series, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Asian Pacific American Archives and Media Center, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Book Collection, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies Minor, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Audre Lorde Project, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Budget Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Budget Proposal, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cantonese I Course: Planning, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cantonese II Course: Approval Form, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Challenge Fund Grant, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Community Documentation and Census 2000, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Co-Sponsorships, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Course Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Course Proposals, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Courses, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Curriculum Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Development: Notes, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Development Correspondence: General, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Development Correspondence: American Express, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Development Correspondence: Anheuser-Busch, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Anna Sui, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Development Correspondence: Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Development Correspondence: Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Development Correspondence: Rockefeller Foundation (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Development Correspondence: Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Development Correspondence: Lucent Technologies, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Development Correspondence: Starr Foundation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Vivienne Tam, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Yahoo, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - End of the Year Party Logistics, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Event: Dangerous Music, Fierce Women, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Event: "Maya Lin: Topologies", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Event Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fall Course Listings, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Faculty (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Faculty-Recruitment and Search (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Faculty-Affiliated and Adjunct (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Intermediate Tagalog II Course Proposal, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Interoffice Memoranda, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Jan Lo Shinebourne Reception, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - JANM Talk, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - JANM/Jewish Talk, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - JANM Workshops, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Keep Event, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Kelly Loves Tony Film Screening, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Kerri Sakamoto Reading, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Letters to Thien Film Screening, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Life After NYU Series, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - NYU Departmental Events, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - NYU Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Open House, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Open House, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Opening of A/P/A Studies Program and Institute, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Program Budget, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Proposed Courses, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Sino-American Training Project, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Small Events and Co-Sponsorships, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - South Asia Pilot, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Spring Courses: Proposals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Spring Reception, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Spring Syllabi, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Summer Course Listings, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Syllabus: Cinema of Asia-America, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Syllabus: Conversational Tagalog I, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Syllabus: Filming Asia America, Documenting Community, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Syllabus: Media and Culture, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Syllabus: Reading Race and Representation (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Tomie Arai Exhibit Opening Reception, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Visiting Faculty Program, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Visiting Scholars: General, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Visiting Scholar: Anju Bhargava, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Visiting Scholar: Doris Lee, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Visiting Scholar: Fabiana Chin, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Visiting Scholar: Gloria Lee, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Visiting Scholar: Grace Hong, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Visiting Scholar: Margo Machida, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Visiting Scholar: Mimi Young, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sonny Ago, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sunaina Maira, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tan A. Lin, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tarry Hum, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tineke Jansen, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Working Sessions, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Subseries D: Syllabi
    Subseries D contains syllabi from classes given at A/P/A.
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series III: Events, 1995-2003
  Series III consists of information regarding various events and activities produced and sponsored by the A/P/A Institute. These records are primarily comprised of outreach materials, such as posters, brochures, and flyers. The majority of these events are art-related, such as gallery exhibitions, author reading series, and film screenings. Events also include lectures and discussions regarding various issues relevant to the A/P/A student community. Many of these events were documented either on film or audio. These recordings are included in the collection. This series is divided into three subseries: a series of general materials organized alphabetically, a series of posters, and a series of general materials organized chronologically. The material in Subseries 3 was received at a later date, and its chronological organization has been retained.
  - Subseries A: General (Alphabetical)
    - A. 100 Gala (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - A Gathering of Tribes, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Alumni Gallery Viewing, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Annual Holiday Party-Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Art Catalogs, 2002-2012 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Artist in Residence, 1 of 2, 1998-2012 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Artist in Residence, 2 of 2, 1999-2012 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Artist in Residence: David Henry Hwang, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Artist in Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Artist in Residence: Ping Chong, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee: Asian Americans and the Vietnam War, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Artist Talk: Mary Ting, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Artist: Dana Tai Soon Burgess and Company, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Artist: Wen Ho Lee, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Artist: Vijai Nathan, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Artist: Susan Sponsler, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Artist: Flo Oy Wong, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Building Bridges, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Freezone, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Pursuit of Pop, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Urbanizasian, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Asians in America Conference Proceedings, 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Asians in America Conference Proceedings, 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Asian Americans in the Arts, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Asian Americans in the Arts, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Reading for Premonitions: The Kaya Anthology of New Asian North American Poetry, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Breaking Stereotypes: Asian Pacific American Musicians, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Gary Okihiro On the Death of Ethnic Studies, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: May Joseph, Migrancy, Citizenship and New York City, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Reclaiming Lives with Ruthanne Lum McCunn, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Re-visioning the City, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Chang-Rae Lee Reading A Gesture Life, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights Issues and Post 9-11 Law Enforcement/Community Relations in New York: A Fact Finding Forum, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Coming of Age in Amelika, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Coming to Terms: The Impact of WWII on American Jews and Japanese Americans Today, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Commencement and Alumni Receptions, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Course Offerings, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Course Offerings, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Course Offerings, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Course Offerings, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Course Offerings, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Course Offerings, 2000-2005 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Course Offerings, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dilemmas of Historical Memory: Locating South Asian Americans in Asian America Lecture, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dog Eat Dog Party with Jessica Hagedorn, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Dogeaters: Conversation with Jessica Hagedorn, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - East of California Conference-President's Dinner, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Educator's Institute on Asian Americans (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Le Thi Diem Thuy, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Staceyann Chin, "I was Born with Two Tongues", 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Suheir Hammad, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Vijay Iyer, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Empire of Care Book Launch with Catherine Ceniza Choy, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Ephemera, 1 of 8, 1999-2007 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Ephemera, 2 of 8, 1999-2011 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Ephemera, 3 of 8, 1998-2013 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Ephemera, 4 of 8, 2002-2012 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Ephemera, 5 of 8, 2001-2011 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Ephemera, 6 of 8, 1999-2011 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Ephemera, 7 of 8, 1997-2012 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Ephemera, 8 of 8, 1999-2011 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Ephemera -- Emergences and Emergencies, New South Asian Film Making from Britain, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Events Calendar and Pan-A-Visions (A/P/A Studies Newsletter), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Events Calendar, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Events Calendar, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Events Calendar, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Events Calendar, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Events Calendar, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Events Calendar, 2004-2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Events Calendar, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Events Calendar, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Events Calendar, 2010-2012 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Film Screening: Global Village or Global Pillage, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Film Screening: Kelly Loves Tony, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Film Screening: Korean Film Festival, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Film Screening: The Game of Their Lives, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Film Screening: Raising Our Voices, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Film Screening: Say I Do, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Film Screening: An Untold Triumph, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Films: Activist Media, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Flower Drum Song Symposium, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Flower Drum Song Press and Release Forms, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 1 of 6, 1997-2012 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 2 of 6, 1998-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 3 of 6, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 5 of 6, 1996-2012 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 6 of 6, 2000-2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Garden of Export Delights with Swati Khurana, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship and Transnationalism, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship and Transnationalism, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - General APA Information, Undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Helen Zia: Asian American Dreams Book Reception, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - I of Beholder Exhibition, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Illiterate Heart by Meena Alexander, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - In the Country of my Imagination, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - In the Country of My Imagination Planning (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Is Charlie Chan Really Dead?: Asians in America Conference, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Kip Fulbeck Exhibition (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Maya Lin at the A/P/A Gallery, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Mind's Desire by Jaishri Abichandani, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-2007 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Momotaro/ Peach Boy: New Works by Tomie Arai, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Museum of Absences/Oveleaf Hong Kong Book Party (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - My Country Versus Me Book Launch, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - My Country Versus Me Planning (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - New York Before Chinatown Book Party, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nori Morimoto Exhibit, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Open House Reception, 1997-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds Symposium, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Palates of Pleasure: The Philosophy and Politics of Southeast Asian Food Symposium, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Palates of Pleasure Fundraising, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Palates of Pleasure Brochures, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A Photographic Journey with Corky Lee, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Please Do Not Throw Peanuts at My God: Installation by Siddhartha Joag, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Politics and Paranoia Conference, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Professional Workshop: Skills for Working in a Multicultural America, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Program and Institute Brochure, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Public Displays of Asianness--A Conference on Asian American Popular Culture, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Race and Social Injustice: The Diallo Verdict Panel Discussion, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Redistricting and "Communities of Interest", 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Resident Aliens Art Installation by Siddhartha Joag and Tomie Arai, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Rethinking Ethnic and Area Studies Conference, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Rethinking New York City: A Post 9-11 Roundtable, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Serene Ford Northington: Getting in the Picture, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Serene Ford Northington: War Retold, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Sia Figel: where we once belonged, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Sino-American Cross Cultural Project, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Social Work Conference, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - South Asian Studies Speaker Series, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - South Asian Studies Speaker Series Leadership Training, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)